[
      {
            "question": "Who are Blossom, Bubbles, and Buttercup?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. The Powerpuff Girls",
                  "B. Ariel's Daughters",
                  "C. Mickey's nieces",
                  "D. Mickey's Daughters"
            ],
            "answer": "A. The Powerpuff Girls"
      },
      {
            "question": "Donald Duck was reportedly banned from finland for which reason?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Because he often swears",
                  "B. Because he never wear his pants",
                  "C. Because he becomes angry so often",
                  "D. Beacuse he always smile"
            ],
            "answer": "B. Because he never wear his pants"
      },
      {
            "question": "What is the dog's name in the series of (Tom and Jerry)?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Ted",
                  "B. Murphy",
                  "C. Spike",
                  "D. Bruno"
            ],
            "answer": "C. Spike"
      },
      {
            "question": "What is the name of the Scooby-Doo's nephew?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Scrappy-Doo",
                  "B. Chubby-Doo",
                  "C. Muggy-Doo",
                  "D. Happy-Doo"
            ],
            "answer": "A. Scrappy-Doo"
      },
      {
            "question": "What is the original name of the Winnie the pooh?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Ted Bear",
                  "B. Christopher Bear",
                  "C. Edward Bear",
                  "D. Wendell Bear"
            ],
            "answer": "C. Edward Bear"
      },
      {
            "question": "Who is responsible for the first version of the Mickey Mouse's voice ?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Roy Disney",
                  "B. Walt Disney",
                  "C. Mortimer Aderson",
                  "D. Bruno"
            ],
            "answer": "B. Walt Disney"
      },
      {
            "question": "What is the name of the Mickey Mouse's girl friend?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Annie",
                  "B. Minnie",
                  "C. Sandra",
                  "D. Miya"
            ],
            "answer": "B. Minnie"
      },
      {
            "question": "Which of the following cartoon character live under the sea in a pineapple?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Squidward",
                  "B. Patrick",
                  "C. Mr Crabs",
                  "D. SpongeBob SquarePants"
            ],
            "answer": "D. SpongeBob SquarePants"
      },
      {
            "question": "The actor behind the voice of the Mickey and Minnie Mouse?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Dated briefly",
                  "B. Are Married",
                  "C. Hate each other",
                  "D. Love each other"
            ],
            "answer": "B. Are Married"
      },
      {
            "question": "The word (simba) comes from which language?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Afrikaans",
                  "B. Swahii",
                  "C. Turkish",
                  "D. Madarin"
            ],
            "answer": "B. Swahii"
      },
      {
            "question": "Disney's beloved Mickey Mouse almost had a diffrent name. What was it?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Melvin Mouse",
                  "B. Marty Mouse",
                  "C. Mike the Mouse",
                  "D. Mortimer Mouse"
            ],
            "answer": "D. Mortimer Mouse"
      },
      {
            "question": "How old was Ariel when she was married Eric in the Little Mermaid?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. 21",
                  "B. 34",
                  "C. 16",
                  "D. 13"
            ],
            "answer": "C. 16"
      },
      {
            "question": "The Lady and The Tramp was almost called?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. The Lady and the Bozo",
                  "B. The lady and the homer",
                  "C. The lady and rags",
                  "D. All of the above"
            ],
            "answer": "D. All of the above"
      },
      {
            "question": "Which princess has very long hair?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Rapunzel",
                  "B. Bella",
                  "C. Tiana",
                  "D. Cindrella"
            ],
            "answer": "A. Rapunzel"
      },
      {
            "question": "Which character was Walt Disney's favorite?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. Mickey Mouse",
                  "B. Goofy",
                  "C. Donald Duck",
                  "D. Minnie Mouse"
            ],
            "answer": "B. Goofy"
      },
      {
            "question": "Popeye has ________ newphews?",
            "options":
            [
                  "A. 2",
                  "B. 5",
                  "C. 3",
                  "D. 4"
            ],
            "answer": "D. 4"
      }
]